fsafeds.com 2016-06-25

# Privacy Statement

                                           Privacy Statement
At ADP Benefit Services KY, Inc., we know how important it is to keep your personal information secure.
ADP is commited to maintaining the confidentiality of information we receive from our customers
and web site users. We have privacy protections built into every aspect of our business operations,
including our Web-based services. This statement is designed to disclose our privacy strategy.
COLLECTED INFORMATION
ADP limits the information collected about you to what is needed for conducting business. For example,
when we provide services to you on behalf of your employer, we may collect information such as
demographic, payroll, banking, and insurance data. We may use this information to process transactions,
respond to inquiries from you or your representative, or to fulfill other administrative requirements. Failure
to provide requested information limits access to the features and services offered by this site.
Technical and navigational information, such as browser type, Internet protocol address, screens viewed,
and average session length, may be collected and used to improve our Web design and functionality.
This data is used only in aggregate and does not reveal individual details about users of our site.
Protection of your data is a core component of our service to you. ADP information protection controls
are maintained in accordance with industry standards and practices, and we adapt our physical,
electronic, and procedural controls to meet changing requirements and advances in technology.
ADP restricts access to information to those individuals in our organization who require that access in
order to provide products and services to you. Our associates are educated regarding their responsibility
to protect your privacy utilizing clear guidelines.
ADP shares collected information with outside parties only as required (1) by law or legal order, or (2) to
fulfill our contracted administrative duties. For example, ADP provides enrollment services that require
transmitting collected demographic, payroll, and insurance data to the employer and applicable insurance
carrier(s). Information collected will not be distributed or shared with any entity for marketing purposes or
for any other purpose outside the scope of our business requirements.
This site may contain links to other web sites. ADP is not responsible for the privacy practices or the
content of these other web sites. Users should check the policy statement of the other sites to understand
their policies. It is the responsibility of the user to keep personal information private and confidential.
If you are a former customer of ADP, your information is treated in the same manner as the information
of current customers.
ONLINE SECURITY
ADP utilizes proven methods to maintain the security of your information during your use of our
services. Highlights of our security include:
      • Internal firewalls
      • Security audits and assessments
      • Secure Socket Layers 3.0 (128-bit data encryption)
      • User-level security controls
ADP offers several options for accessing your account information, including Web access, automated
telephone service, customer service representative, mail, and e-mail. Specific addresses and telephone
numbers are listed on your statements and other correspondence.
If you have questions or comments regarding this privacy policy, please contact privacy@adp.com.
       CORPORATE HEADQUARTERS / 11405 BLUEGRASS PARKWAY / LOUISVILLE, KY 40299 / 877-372-3337
                         © 2012 ADP BENEFIT SERVICES KY, INC. ALL RIGHTS RESERVED
